<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>economic on Anak Wannaphaschaiyong</title>
    <link>https://awannaphasch2016.github.io/tags/economic/</link>
    <description>Recent content in economic on Anak Wannaphaschaiyong</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://awannaphasch2016.github.io/tags/economic/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Evolution of Asset Transaction</title>
      <link>https://awannaphasch2016.github.io/posts/evolution-of-asset-transaction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://awannaphasch2016.github.io/posts/evolution-of-asset-transaction/</guid>
      <description>Hello, guys
This essay is my interpretation of a discussion on &amp;ldquo;NFTing the World for the General Good&amp;rdquo; episode on Real Vision TV. The information in the essay are adapted to fit rational narrative that I have in my brain.
This is the beginning of the essay.
The four phases are categorized into the following
 transaction an physical assets transaction of electron transaction of information transaction of digital assets  Each phase increase efficiency of transactions which depends on three factors: object, process, and rules.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Incentives Of Owning Money.</title>
      <link>https://awannaphasch2016.github.io/posts/incentives-of-owning-money/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://awannaphasch2016.github.io/posts/incentives-of-owning-money/</guid>
      <description>Edit History  last edit on [2022-07-30 Sat]    Money is the most flexible medium of exchange. For more detail please refer to my blog named &amp;ldquo;Money Is A Type of Token.&amp;rdquo;
Motivation drive efforts. Effort is a seed of creation and innovation. It just happens that money provides universal motivation due to its utility which is measured by speed of conversion from itself to other assets. Money has fastest conversion rates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Money Is A Type Of Token.</title>
      <link>https://awannaphasch2016.github.io/posts/money-is-a-type-of-token/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://awannaphasch2016.github.io/posts/money-is-a-type-of-token/</guid>
      <description>Edit History  last edit on [2022-07-30 Sat] I can refine this blog more by consolidating the current content to my notes on roam research. I don&amp;rsquo;t have time to do this at the time of writing.      In theory, there is no need for &amp;ldquo;medium&amp;rdquo; of exchange. Any exchange can be anything as long as seller and buyer agree upon. Therefore, one can argue that there will always exist a sequence of exchanges of agreements that satisfy any pair of sellers and buyers.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>